{
    "id": "64b931a1c7e14678a61cb9d205f8be0f",
    "title": "Word Forms Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "If you ………………….. the dog, it may bite you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "provoke",
                "provocative",
                "provocation"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "22d32181182541729b4f334c959841dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "The old woman looked at the crowds and the traffic in ......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bewilder",
                "bewildered",
                "bewilderment"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b2e4d8bd99a744e789b400cf22950c67"
        },
        {
            "question": "The actor ………………… aimed at becoming a great singer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wistful",
                "wistfully",
                "wistfulness"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "96e51866d4ae45b0a96994ad5a95ff1f"
        },
        {
            "question": "We expect the authorities to investigate the case ......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "thorough",
                "thoroughly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "10318cee00a34528926272749e58ceb7"
        },
        {
            "question": "His ...................... with work affected his family life.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "preoccupy",
                "preoccupied",
                "preoccupation"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6eee726f7d7f411182117179204f5701"
        },
        {
            "question": "His ...................... with the sage changed his outlook.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "associate",
                "associative",
                "association"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "996592bc705549c694133006c077b9a3"
        },
        {
            "question": "My mother is my biggest …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "inspire",
                "inspirational",
                "inspiration"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3eba43f6f44c4037bfd22c09d1d050b9"
        },
        {
            "question": "The floods caused a great deal of ..................... in many parts of the country.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "destroy",
                "destruct",
                "destruction"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5ba689934d37426bb1a5b61a604fe66f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The robbers tried to …………………. the traveler.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "threat",
                "threatened",
                "threaten"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "61c98d57f5ae46be89fcc8578a52ffdc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Although his first few attempts were not .....................…, he did not lose heart.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "success",
                "successful",
                "succeed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "89d9dcd426124c33b7194337c4828e16"
        }
    ]
}